{
  "exercises": [
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The child’s car is red",
      "answer": "das auto des kindes ist rot"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The mother’s car is blue",
      "answer": "das auto der mutter ist blau"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The mother’s pen is black",
      "answer": "der stift der mutter ist schwarz"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The child’s ball is green",
      "answer": "der ball des kindes ist grün"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The father’s house is big",
      "answer": "das haus des vaters ist groß"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The teacher’s book is old",
      "answer": "das buch des lehrers ist alt"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The student’s room is small",
      "answer": "das zimmer des schülers ist klein"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The man’s dog is white",
      "answer": "der hund des mannes ist weiß"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The woman’s cat is gray",
      "answer": "die katze der frau ist grau"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The boy’s ball is blue",
      "answer": "der ball des jungen ist blau"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The girl’s doll is beautiful",
      "answer": "die puppe des mädchens ist schön"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: Hasan’s car is black",
      "answer": "das ist hasans auto"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: Ankit’s book is new",
      "answer": "das buch ankits ist neu"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The father’s pen is blue",
      "answer": "der stift des vaters ist blau"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The teacher’s table is brown",
      "answer": "der tisch des lehrers ist braun"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The child’s school is near",
      "answer": "die schule des kindes ist nah"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The brother’s ball is big",
      "answer": "der ball des bruders ist groß"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The sister’s book is expensive",
      "answer": "das buch der schwester ist teuer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The dog’s house is small",
      "answer": "das haus des hundes ist klein"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The teacher’s car is green",
      "answer": "das auto des lehrers ist grün"
    }
  ]
}
